Chris Davis

Portland, OR | 360•339•3551 chrismd09@gmail.com

Profile __

I am a recent graduate with an MS in Data Analytics interested in finding a growth-oriented position to apply my experience and new skill-set. My interests include predictive modeling, ML, statistical analysis, and building methods to visualize and tell stories with data.

Education ___

MS Data Analytics 2021

Western Governors University

BBA Operations and Technology Mgmt.

2013

University Of Portland

Toolbox ___

Skills	Code	Software		Libraries	
Data Cleaning	Python	PyCharm	Anaconda	Pandas	NumPy
Predictive Modeling	SQL	Git	Jupyter	SK-Learn	Keras
Data Analysis	R	Spyder	Github	Dash	Plotly
Dashboard Creation	VBA	Tableau	Excel	statsmodels	Matplotlib

Experience _____

Manager, Digital Operations

Mar 2020 - Dec 2020

adidas

- · Manage payment systems and performance for North American markets
- Define payment KPIs/targets and develop internal/vendor level reporting processes
- Analyze payment related bugs and provide detailed resolution requirements
- · Collaborate with vendors to address performance issues, diagnose errors, and develop enhancements
- Identify opportunities and manage the implementation of new payment types/features

Asst. Manager, Platform Operations

Jan 2018 – Mar 2020

adidas

- Manage e-commerce fraud mitigation and payment performance for the US market
- · Respond to new fraud attacks. Vulnerability analysis, rule ideation, and performance analysis
- · Work with global teams to request enhancements, define requirements, and assist implementations
- Resolve site bugs and other operations related issues as requested by CS, HR, IT, Mktg. etc.

Business Analyst Jan 2014 – Jul 2015

The Clymb

- Develop and report weekly operations metrics
- Build out dynamic dashboards to provide live data access
- Perform ad-hoc queries/analysis as requested by several teams

Operations Coordinator

May 2013 - Jan 2014

The Clymb

- Automate excel workflows using VBA
- · Manage the receipt of product correctly into inventory and into the product information database